JENNY HANLON

UX/UI DESIGNER

SKILLS

RESEARCH

Heuristic Analysis User Survey & Interview Persona Development User Stories User Flows

DESIGN

Site Mapping
Lo/Hi-fidelity Wireframing
Logo & Branding
Style Guide
Interactive Prototyping
Usability Testing
Balsamiq
Photoshop/Illustrator/Sketch
InVision

DEVELOPMENT

HTML/CSS JavaScript, jQuery, Angular.js

EDUCATION

DESIGN APPRENTICESHIP

June 2015 - Jan 2016 Bloc, Inc. - San Francisco

BA, INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS

Aug 2003 - May 2007 University of Colorado - Boulder

PROFILE

A researcher and problem solver at heart with a passion for crafting seamless interfaces and clean, polished visuals. Firsthand understanding of business requirements, goals, and development brings specialized insight into UX practices. Innate empathy produces elegant results for users and clients alike.

EXPERIENCE

OWNER, PHOTOGRAPHER

Jenny Hanlon Photography | 2010 - 2015

- Independently built a thriving boutique business focused on providing clients with the utmost quality in care, service, and photographic art.
- Conceptualized, directed, & photographed hundreds of lifestyle shoots and over 60 wedding celebrations.
- Honed mastery of lighting, composure, color theory, and information architecture of visual art.

COPYWRITER

Freelance | 2010 - 2012

• Composed and edited publications for various companies and organizations regarding leadership, cultural trends, youth curriculum, blogs, and marketing copy.

MARKETING SPECIALIST

Fellowship of Catholic University Students | 2008 - 2010

- Worked with talented communications team to grow FOCUS' national presence by 93%.
- Wrote and edited all web and print content.